<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Hi, I&#39;m ef_</title>
    <link>http://dailyprog.org/~ef/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Hi, I&#39;m ef_</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; &lt;a href=&#34;http://dailyprog.org/~ef&#34;&gt;ef_&lt;/a&gt; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 10:42:56 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dailyprog.org/~ef/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding Problematic Values (Part 3)</title>
      <link>http://dailyprog.org/~ef/posts/finding-problematic-values-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 10:42:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dailyprog.org/~ef/posts/finding-problematic-values-part-3/</guid>
      <description>Takeaway Continue your understanding of not relying on in-your-face values.
Challenges  Fencepost error Finding illogical values through strategy  Setup  Windows 10 x64 FCEUX 2.2.3 M.C. Kids for NES Cheat Engine 6.8.1 x64  Prerequisites  Scanning simple values and types from parts 1 and 2.  Hacking M.C. Kids Health (hearts) Same as before:
 Scan Type: Unknown initial value; followed by Increased Value, Decreased Value, and Unchanged Value Value Type: All  Tip!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Features of a Chat UI (Part 2)</title>
      <link>http://dailyprog.org/~ef/posts/2-features-of-a-chat-ui/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 03:21:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dailyprog.org/~ef/posts/2-features-of-a-chat-ui/</guid>
      <description>In this article I&amp;rsquo;ll focus on figuring out the features.
Suggestion Gathering I have free reign over the UI. While I&amp;rsquo;m dealing with other people&amp;rsquo;s suggestions, there are no requirements in place to dissuade anything I come up with. The main thing to consider are the users&amp;rsquo; interests, including mine. Dailyprog is a platform focused on anonymity, where Dailyprog users are still highly interested in being contacted in private. A throwaway email created specifically for one website is useful but is annoying to maintain on a user&amp;rsquo;s end; and it&amp;rsquo;s a huge disconnect from the site where the user&amp;rsquo;s work is showcased.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developing Chat UI (Part 1)</title>
      <link>http://dailyprog.org/~ef/posts/developing-chat-ui/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 14:59:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dailyprog.org/~ef/posts/developing-chat-ui/</guid>
      <description>I recently tasked myself a project to develop the UI for a chat client that will later become a part of the Dailyprog/Hackerchan. As of now, a lot of the technical details are open in the air. I&amp;rsquo;m not even sure if it will use IRC in the end. The IRC part came from needing to replace the current Kiwi IRC client.
I&amp;rsquo;m not really a front end guy, but sometimes I can enjoy it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Importance of Value Types (Part 2)</title>
      <link>http://dailyprog.org/~ef/posts/importance-value-types/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 00:46:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dailyprog.org/~ef/posts/importance-value-types/</guid>
      <description>Setup  Windows 10 x64 FCEUX 2.2.3 Ninja Gaiden 2 for NES Cheat Engine 6.8.1 x64  Prerequisite  Knowledge of scanning simple values. See: Intro Scan Types  The Value Type Before, I only paid attention to the Scan Type, where I said it&amp;rsquo;s always best to leave it at Unknown initial value. No need to know anything about assembly or how bytes are stored. The next step is Value Type, which is important and needs some explanation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Scan Types (Part 1)</title>
      <link>http://dailyprog.org/~ef/posts/intro-scan-types/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 11:32:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dailyprog.org/~ef/posts/intro-scan-types/</guid>
      <description>A Little Background I&amp;rsquo;ve always been interested in knowing how to hack. It&amp;rsquo;s what got me interested in programming, and it started out with wanting to gain advantages in games. Though now I&amp;rsquo;ve become interested in further improving my knowledge and skills in computer science. With this series of hacking articles, I plan to write about my journey. I want to challenge myself in different areas (writing, programming, thinking, explaining), make this a hobby, and improve my writing skills.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>